MP3
to Ajay
Hello friends, welcome to our
channel in a tips and tricks and this is
our playlist Captain Market.
Today in our playlist we are going to talk
about the dividend of ICICI Lombard company. What is the record date of the case
and how much dividend has
this company decided to give. Let's watch this video
in detail and
watch the entire video to know the complete details. And those who have
come to my channel or this video for the first time, do
not forget to subscribe
because I keep bringing similar trending videos, so I keep
uploading them on my channel.
If you want notifications or any
such notifications, then
you will have to press the 'click' button. So let's
start without any delay. So first of all let's
talk about
what ICICI Lambert company does.
ICICI Bank Lambert Company
is a 11 year old general insurance company which declares a dividend of ₹5
per equity share of ₹10 face value for the financial year ending 31 March 2019. Did
you understand?  It is trying to say that the
financial year ended on 31 March 2019
declares a dividend at the rate of ₹5 per equity share of ₹10 face value. The
company, while informing the BSE, has
said that it has fixed the record date for this dividend as
19 July 2022. Yes, you heard it right, 19
July 2022,
that is, the shareholders who will have the
shares of the company till 29 July 2022 will be
given the dividend. Okay, and let me tell
you that
ICICI Lombard General Insurance
is a red scam company of the financial sector,
whose market value is 61 thousand six hundred
twenty-one crore rupees. It is one of the top
private general insurance companies in India,
which provides various types of insurance. It
also provides services like automobile, health, travel
business corporation and cyber insurance. The
share of ICICI Lombard General Insurance closed at Rs
1251 with a gain of 0.04 percent in trading on Friday.
This stock had closed at Rs 1251 level last year.
In one year, it has broken 17 point 6820, which
means it is surrounded, whereas in this year 2022, it will
bring 11 point 26. At the current market price, this
stock is seen above its 80-week active S and hundred
days movie average.
Understand this and friends, if
we look at the 52-week high by taking a stop below the day, it
is at Rs 1675, whereas if you
look at its 2052, it is
1071 above. If you liked this video of mine,
then please like this video and
share it with your friends to whom
you have told in your share market, stock market,
trading market, exchange market
that yes, I invest, I
invest, okay, so let's
meet you again in the next video. Then
take care of bird
Ajay
[Music]